Can I see the comics?
可以给我看漫画吗？
This is the New York Times.
这是纽约时报
Okay,may I see the comics?
好，能否借我看漫画？
I thought you were taking Ross to the game.
你们不是要带罗斯去看球？
-We are. He's meeting us here. -No,Rachel's meeting us here!
是啊，我们约在这里 瑞秋也跟我们约在这里
Come on! They can be in the same room.
他们还是可以共处一室吧
-You should've been there last night. -What happened?
你昨晚没看到 怎么了？
Ross was hanging out at our place.
罗斯在我们那边
Rachel comes over to borrow some moisturizer from Chandler
瑞秋来跟钱德借润肤乳…
How hard is it to say "something"?
你不能说借“东西”吗？
Rachel came over to borrow "something."
瑞秋过来借“东西”
Anyway,her and Ross just started yelling at each other.
反正她和罗斯就开始对骂
Why was he yelling at her? He slept with someone else.
他怎么敢骂她？ 他跟别人上床耶
He says they were on a break when it happened...
他说他们当时分手了
...so she should've forgiven him by now.
所以她早就该原谅他了
He is so unreasonable! God!
他真不可理喻，真是的
Although I understand what he means.
不过我了解他的意思
Oh,my God! This is like 60 Minutes...
天哪，这样好像“60分钟”
...when at first you're mad that pharmaceutical company made the drug.
你本来很气制药公司 生产一种药
And then,you just feel bad for the people,because...
后来又很同情那些人，因为…
...they needed to make their hair grow.
他们想要长头发
You know,this is like when my parents got divorced.
我父母离婚时就是这样
I hope Ross doesn't try to kidnap me after Cub Scouts.
希望罗斯看完球 不会企图绑架我
I dreamed that Ross and Rachel were still together.
我梦到罗斯和瑞秋没有分手
And we were all hanging out and happy.
我们开心的在一起
I had the same dream.
我也梦到了
-And nobody slept with the xerox girl. -Oh,I had the opposite dream.
没有人跟那个女的上床 我的刚好相反
Maybe it's gonna be okay. I mean,it's been a week.
也许不要紧，都一个星期了
It never takes me more than a week to get over a relationship.
我结束一段感情 从不超过一星期
It never takes you more than a shower to get over a relationship.
你一冲完澡 一段感情就结束了
Let's go! Let's hit the road. Let's get the show on it.
走吧，上路了，我们去玩吧
Let me get coffee.
我先喝杯咖啡
I know the best coffeehouse. And it's close.
附近有一家很棒的咖啡馆
Closer than here?
比这里近？
Oh,look! I found coffee!
你看，我找到一杯
Okay,let's skedaddle.
我们走吧
I'm not gonna drink somebody's old coffee.
我才不喝别人喝剩的
Okay,Your Highness.
是，殿下
"Rachel,I'm really sorry." "Okay,Ross. Wanna get back together?"
“瑞秋，对不起” “没关系，你想复合吗？”
"Yeah,okay."
“好啊”
Did anyone else hear that?
你们有听到吗？
The One Without the Ski Trip
本集播出：“左右为难”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
Is he here?
他在吗？
Here's your moisturizer.
你的润肤乳
You guys are gonna love me! Okay,check it out.
你们会爱死我！听我说
Thursday night,five tickets.
周四晚上，五张票
Calvin Klein lingerie show, and you guys are coming with me.
卡文克莱内衣秀 你们要跟我一起去
I said that out loud,right?
我有说出声音来吧？
Yes,it's just that we kind of already...
有，只是我们已经…
... made plans with Ross.
跟罗斯有约了
Well,okay.
好吧
Well,there you go.
就这样吧
It's just,he got this new home-theater dealy...
他买了新的家庭剧院组合
...and he wants us to check it out.
想找我们去看
He's excited about it too.
他很兴奋
He even recorded showtimes on his answering machine.
还在答录机里录了节目表
-We're sorry,honey. -Oh,it's okay.
对不起 没关系
Rach,it's not that we don't want to. Really.
不是我们不想去，真的
Are we talking models in their underwear?
模特儿穿内衣走秀？
And heels.
还有高跟鞋
Ross did ask us first, and we set that night aside.
罗斯先开口，我们也排好了
Come on. If he asked you first, it's only fair.
没关系，是他先约的，很公平
Oh,boy,do I feel bad!
我好受不了
Very bad.
非常受不了
Chandler,what are you doing?
钱德，你在干什么？
Oh,my God!
天哪
You're smoking again?
你又抽烟了？
Well,actually, yesterday,I was smoking again.
那是昨天
Today I'm smoking,still.
今天是“还在抽”
Why would you start again after chewing all that quitting gum?
嚼了那么多戒烟口香糖 为什么又开始抽了？
This is just like my parents' divorce...
我父母离婚时就像这样
...which is when I first started smoking.
害我学会抽烟
Weren't you 9?
你不是才9岁？
I'm telling you something, that first smoke after naptime....
午睡后来一根最过瘾
That's great. With my luck,that's him.
帅啊，我猜是他
Him? Ross?
罗斯？
No,"Hymn" 253: "His Eyes Are on the Sparrow."
不，是赞美诗253篇 “爱的恩泽”
When my parents got divorced,I started using humor as a defense mechanism.
我父母离婚后 我开始用幽默来自卫
Hi. Do you guys have weekend plans?
你们周末有计划吗？
Because my sister says we can spend the weekend at her cabin,skiing.
我妹说周末 可以到她的小屋去滑雪
I'm asking you first,right? I'm playing by the rules.
是我先问的吧？ 我有遵守游戏规则
Absolutely.
没问题
Chandler! You're smoking? What are you doing?
钱德，你抽烟？你怎么搞的？
Shut up! You're not my real mom!
闭嘴，你又不是我的亲娘
Could you close that window? My nipples could cut glass!
关窗子好吗？ 我的乳头硬到可以割玻璃
Really? Because mine get me out of tickets.
真的？我的让我躲掉罚单
Look,I just wanna say I really appreciate you spending time with me.
真的很谢谢你们来陪我
It's been a hard time right now, so I just want to say thanks.
这阵子很难熬，真的谢谢你们
Somebody else hug him. I have to stay by the window.
谁去抱抱他 我得留在窗子旁边
How about this weekend,we have a laser-disc marathon,okay?
周末要不要来个影碟马拉松？
And maybe a tournament on my new...
或是来比赛，我有新的…
...dart board! What do you think?
飞镖盘！怎么样？
Two days of darts! It'll be great!
连射两天飞镖，一定很好玩
It'll be great for next weekend.
不如排在下周末
This weekend,guys.
不，这个周末
It'll be great for next weekend.
不如排在下周末
I mean,"lt'll be great."
一定会很好玩
What's going on?
怎么回事？
We're sort of invited to go skiing. You know,Rachel's sister's cabin?
我们被找去滑雪 要去瑞秋的妹妹的小屋
So,for the whole weekend?
整个周末？
We're really sorry, but she did ask us first.
对不起，是她先约的
That's okay. If you all have to go away...
没关系，我失恋的第一个周末
...for the first weekend I'm alone by myself...
你们都要出城去
...then I totally understand.
我完全可以理解
I can stay. I'm gonna stay.
我可以留下来，我留下来
The last time I went, I was afraid to leave the chair lift.
上次去滑雪 我根本不敢下吊车
I just went round and round.
就这样坐来坐去
We need you to drive us there in your grandmother's cab.
你得开你奶奶的车载我们去
-But you know what? I'll stay. -No,I'll stay. He's my brother.
这样吧，我留下来 不，我留，他是我的哥哥
What,a "pity stay"?
这是同情吗？
We're gonna have fun!
我们会玩得很开心
We can make fudge.
我们来做牛奶软糖
Pity food?
同情的食物？
You know what? I don't need any of you to stay.
没关系，我不需要你们留下来
Nobody stays.
谁都不准留下来
Well,then,I might as well offer to stay.
那我也表示一下好了
Does anybody else feel bad about Ross?
有人在替罗斯难过吗？
You think he's still mad?
你觉得他还在生气？
He's probably more mad since you called him to borrow his goggles.
更气了，你居然跟他借护目镜
What? Mine aren't tinted.
怎样？我的没有颜色
What?
怎样？
What does the sign say?
标示说什么？
"Beam me up,Jesus."
“主耶稣，请照耀我”
The "No Smoking" sign.
是“禁止吸烟”的标示
There's no smoking in my grandmother's cab.
我奶奶的车上不能抽烟
Well,then,I have to go to the bathroom.
那我要上厕所
Oh,please!
拜托
No unscheduled stops. You can go when we stop for gas.
没事不准停车 加油的时候再去
There's a rest stop right up there. Come on,I really have to go!
那边有休息站 我真的得上厕所
Oh,now I have to go!
现在我也想上了
Here we go.
到了
-Brace yourself! -What?
坐好 什么？
-Aren't you gonna go? -No,thanks.
你不去？ 不了
Rachel never pees in public restrooms.
瑞秋不上公共厕所
They never have any paper in there.
里面都没有卫生纸
So my rule is,"No tissue,no tushy."
所以我决定 没有面纸就不嘘嘘
Well,if everybody's going....
既然大家都下车了…
Don't close it! The keys are in there!
别关门！钥匙在里面
-What's going on? -My lighter's in there!
怎么了？ 打火机在里面
Damn! The tailpipe's not hot enough to light this.
妈的 排气管不够烫，点不着
I can open this. Anybody got a coat hanger?
我会开门，谁有衣架？
Oh,I do.
我有
No,I took it out of my shirt when I put it on this morning.
不对，早上穿衣服时拿掉了
So if your parents hadn't divorced...
要是你的父母没有离婚
...you'd be able to answer a question like a normal person?
你就能正常的回答问题？
Look,I just need a wire something to jimmy it.
我需要铁丝类的东西把它撬开
One of you give me your bra underwire.
把你们内衣的钢丝给我
Come on! Who has the biggest boobs?
快，谁的胸部最大？
Whoever has the biggest boobs, has the biggest bra and wire.
胸部最大，内衣的钢丝也最长
-No! -It's too expensive!
不要 很贵耶
To get back in the car, we need that wire.
有钢丝才能回车上
Your call.
你们决定
Monica's are the biggest.
摩妮卡最大
These tiny little non-breasts? Please! It's gotta be Rachel.
这两粒小红豆？拜托！ 绝对是瑞秋
No,mine are deceptively small.
不对，我的是骗人的
I mean,I actually sometimes stuff my bra.
我有时候还会垫东西
Well,then,your bra would still be big.
所以你的内衣还是很大
No,I stuff outside the bra.
我都垫在内衣外面
Ladies,let's just compromise,okay?
小姐们，你们就让步吧
Phoebe,Rachel, take off Monica's bra.
菲比、瑞秋 脱了摩妮卡的胸罩
All right,forget it,never mind.
好啦，算了
-You can have mine. -Thank you.
我脱 谢谢
What are you doing? There's a trash can right there.
你干什么？那里就有垃圾桶
I thought if I littered,that crying lndian might come by and save us.
我想引来印地安人 这样就有救了
There.
拿去
Thank you,Phoebe. That's very,very generous.
菲比，谢了，你真大方
Now,let's decide who has the nicest ass.
现在来比谁的屁股翘
And there you go!
上车吧
Well,at least let me smoke it to the good part!
至少让我爽一下
-What's going on? -What?
怎么搞的？ 怎么了？
Yeah,this has happened before.
我碰过这种状况
-So you know how to fix it? -Yep. Put more gas in.
那你会修罗？ 会，加油
Hi. What are you doing here?
你怎么来了？
I was wondering, when you and I split up...
我在想，我们分手时
...did you get the tape that was half the last episode of M.A. S.H...
你有没有分到一卷带子 录了最后一集的“外科医生”
...and half the hostages coming home?
和人质回国的新闻？
But now it's Susan and me in Mexico and the hostages coming home.
现在是苏珊和我游墨西哥 和人质回国的新闻
Where's Ben?
班呢？
He's sleeping.
在睡觉
Is this a bad time?
我来得不是时候？
Yeah,actually. Susan's gonna be here any minute.
没错，苏珊马上就要来了
It's kind of an anniversary.
今天是个纪念日
I thought you guys got married in January.
你们不是一月结婚？
A different kind of anniversary.
是另一个纪念日
So anyway
总之…
Candles,champagne....
蜡烛、香槟
Yeah,anniversaries are great...
纪念日真好
... because love lasts forever, you know?
因为爱是永恒的
There's nothing like it in this life. Money in the bank.
什么也比不上爱情可靠
So Rachel and I broke up.
瑞秋和我分手了
God,Ross,I am so sorry!
天哪，真可惜
You know what?
你知道吗？
I wanna talk about this so much...
我很想陪你聊一聊
... but when we can really get into it.
但要找个能长谈的时间
-You free for dinner tomorrow? -I'd love that.
明天晚餐可以吗？ 太好了
Me too.
我也是
I guess it all started when Rachel got this new job.
一切都是因为瑞秋找到新工作
Triple A can pick us up.
汽车协会可以来载我们
What town are we near?
我们靠近哪个镇？
Freemont.
佛利蒙特
Westmont.
威斯蒙特
Westberg?
威斯柏格？
Why are you answering?
不知道就别说
Do you know what route we're on?
我们在哪条路上？
We are definitely on Route 27.
绝对是27号公路
We are at a rest stop on Route 27
我们在27号公路一个休息站
There is no Route 27.
没有27号公路
-Either 93 or 76. -I don't know.
不是93号就是76号 我不知道
I always slept in the back when we drove here.
我每次来都在后座睡觉
Can you just send someone up and down 76 and check every rest stop?
能不能请人 沿着76号公路找？
And also 93?
还有93号公路？
No,they don't do that.
他们不干
Somebody will come and save us.
一定会有人来救我们
Who? Have you seen a car in the last hour and a half?
谁？这一个半小时 有车子经过吗？
We should call Ross. Maybe he can get a car to get us.
应该找罗斯 他可以借车来载我们
I am not getting in a car with Ross!
我不要跟罗斯同车
We will just have to...
我们必须…
...Iive here!
耗在这里
-But it's so cold. -No!
但是好冷 不行
I won't get in a car with him. Think of something else.
我不跟他同车，想别的办法
Joey and Chandler are back!
乔伊和钱德回来了
So the "going for help" went well?
求援过程很顺利？
Smokey Joe here got halfway to the highway and collapsed.
老烟枪走到一半就挂了
I have the lung capacity of a 2-year-old.
我的肺活量跟两岁小孩一样
Then why are you smoking?
那你为什么要抽烟？
It's very unsettling.
我很不安
Right? I mean, it's pretty unbelievable.
对吧？真是太扯了
They just took off, without even looking back.
他们就这样头也不回的出发
I don't need them. I've got you guys now as friends.
我不需要他们 我有你们这些朋友
You and Susan.
你和苏珊
Susan will be so pleased.
苏珊会很高兴
Seven-one-seven?
717？
Where's 717?
717是哪里？
You have more of these for Susan,right?
你有帮苏珊留吧？
No,but that's okay.
没有，不过没关系
I'll just put out pickles or something.
还有酸黄瓜可以吃
-Ross,thank God! -Pheebs?
罗斯，谢天谢地 菲比？
Why are you whispering?
为什么这么小声？
I ate a bug.
我吃了一只虫子
Hey,Rach! The tampons here are only a penny.
瑞秋，这里的棉条只要一毛钱
Let's stock up.
我们买来屯积
We're out of gas and don't know where we are so we can't get a tow truck.
我们没油了，又不知道方位 没办法叫拖车
Now you want a favor?
现在需要帮忙了？
Yes,please.
对，拜托
I'm sorry your car broke down,Pheebs...
很抱歉你们的车子挂了
... but I'm too busy with some of my real friends right now.
但是我忙着跟真朋友联络感情
But please call to let me know you got home safely.
等你们安全到家，记得通知我
Phoebe,hang on a second.
菲比，等一下
Take my car. Get your friends.
开我的车去接你朋友
No,I won't pick them up.
我才不要去接他们
We both know you'll do it, because you're not a jerk.
我们都知道你会去 因为你不是混蛋
So you can sulk here for half an hour, then go get them...
你顶多再骂个半小时 还是会去接他们
-...or save time and sulk in the car. -Rachel doesn't
不如节省时间去车上骂 瑞秋不会…
I'm sorry Rachel dumped you for Mark...
很遗撼瑞秋为了马克甩了你
...and you're the innocent victim in this.
你是无辜的受害者
But don't punish your friends for what Rachel did.
但不要为了瑞秋牵怒你的朋友
Yeah,you're right.
你说得对
Phoebe,hang on. Ross wants to say something.
菲比，等一下，罗斯要跟你说
What?
什么？
You slept with someone else?
你跟别人上床？
We were on a break!
我们当时在分手状态
We were
我们…
Where are you? I'll find you.
你们在哪里？我去找
You slept with another woman?
你跟别的女人上床？
Oh,you're one to talk.
你还敢说
Okay,done!
好了
What's "pleh"?
什么是“命救”？
That's "help" spelled backwards...
就是“救命”反过来
...so that the helicopters can read it from the air.
好让直升机上的人看得懂
What's "dufus" spelled backwards?
“呆子”反过来怎么写？
Car! Car!
有车子！
Oh,it's Ross on one of his drives!
罗斯出来兜风了
What is he doing here?
他来干什么？
He is saving your butt.
他来救你们一命
Unless I'm stepping on some toes here...
除非我惹到了某个人
...in which case I could just mosey on.
那我可以闪人
I have plenty of people to help on the interstate.
州际公路上有很多人需要帮助
-Come on! -We need your help,please!
别这样 我们需要你
Fine! Fine!
好好好
Oh,no! Now it's not gonna make any sense.
完了，别人会看不懂
You guys...
喂…
...what do we do about Ross? He drove all the way up here.
罗斯怎么办？他大老远跑来
Just send him back, then we'll go skiing?
难道要叫他回去 我们自己去滑雪？
This is horrible. It's just horrible.
烦死了
Should we ask Ross to come along?
要找罗斯一起去吗？
But what about Rachel? How are we gonna even ask her?
那瑞秋呢？要怎么向她开口？
Ask me what?
开什么口？
If it might be okay if Ross came skiing?
罗斯能不能去滑雪？
No,I wasn't gonna ask that.
我才没有要问
You guys are unbelievable. No,he cannot come!
你们太扯了 不行，他不能去
-Excuse me? -It's horrible!
什么？ 烦死了
Oh,please? Can't I come to your special,magical cabin?
求求你，让我去你的神奇小屋
Why would you even want to come? You're a horrible skier.
你去干什么？你滑雪滑得很烂
Hitting me where it hurts! My ski skills!
真是说到我的痛处啊！
Here we go again.
又来了
I can't handle this,you guys.
我没办法处理
I can handle it. "Handle" is my middle name.
我有办法 “处理”是我的名字
Actually,it's the middle part of my first name.
我的名字去头去尾就是处理
All right,Pheebs,your cab's ready.
菲比，你的车子好了
Let's go.
走吧
You're welcome.
不客气
I'm sorry. Were you speaking to me, or sleeping with someone else?
抱歉，你在跟我说话 还是跟别人上床？
We were on a break!
我们当时分手了
Why don't you just put that on your answering machine?
你干脆在答录机里留这句话
It's valid,and I'm not the only one who thinks so.
本来就是，不只我这么想
Monica agrees with me.
摩妮卡也同意
What?
什么？
I don't know.
我不知道
You said it last night.
你昨晚说的
What I said was that I understood.
我是说我能理解
Joey is the one who agreed with you.
乔伊才认同你
Really,Joey?
是吗，乔伊？
What?
什么？
You know what? There is no right or wrong here.
这件事没有对错
I think it's very obvious who's wrong here.
我觉得错的是谁很明显
Obviously not to Joey.
乔伊不这么想
What?
什么？
-Joey and Monica feel the way I do! -You and this innocent puppy act!
乔伊和摩妮卡跟我感觉一样 你只会装无辜
Hey,guess who I am?
你们猜我在学谁？
Look what you're doing to Chandler!
你们把钱德害得多惨！
Look. We know that this is really,really hard for you guys.
听着，我们知道你们都很难受
You don't have to love each other.
你们不必爱对方
You don't even have to like each other much right now.
你们现在甚至不必喜欢对方
But please,find a way to be around each other.
但是请设法和平相处
And not put us in the middle.
别让我们左右为难
Otherwise,I mean,that's just it for us hanging out together.
否则我们以后就不用在一起了
Is that what you want?
你们真的想这样？
Can you be civil?
讲理一点好吗？
I can.
我可以
Good,let's get back in the car. It's freezing...
很好，回车上吧，冷死了
...and my chest is unsupported.
我的胸部又吊在那边
Wait a second!
等一下
I mean,what are we doing? Who's going with who?
现在是怎样？谁要跟谁走？
Look,you guys should go.
你们去吧
You know, you planned this all out...
你们都计划好了
...and I don't wanna ruin it. So just go.
我不想破坏，你们去吧
You drove all the way up here.
你大老远开车来
I've got to take the car back anyway.
反正我得去还车
I'm spending all day tomorrow with Ben.
我明天一整天都要陪班
It's fine,okay? Just go. No guilt,I promise.
没关系，你们去吧 不要有罪恶感，真的
Thank you.
谢谢
We'll call you when we get back.
回去再打电话给你
Maybe we can,like, go to a movie or something.
我们可以去看电影
Or the rodeo!
或是去看马术表演
That would be great.
听起来不错
I was being Shelley Winters from The Poseidon Adventure.
我在学“海神号”雪莉温特斯
I know.
我知道
Bye!
再见
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
抱歉这么晚
Were you sleeping?
你在睡觉？
Oh,great.
那就好
I had to get you a new battery. I got the best I could.
你的车子得换电池 我换了一个最好的
You don't want to skimp there.
这种钱不能省
You're a genius.
你真聪明
It came to about $112.
花了112元
But what the hell, call it an even 110?
算了，算110就好
I'll pay you tomorrow. Bye!
明天给你，再见
So they all took off.
他们都走了
It was pretty hard watching them go,you know?
看他们离开蛮难受的
Yeah,okay. Bye.
好，再见
So I'm gonna take off then.
那我走罗